Guide to the Amos Niven Wilder and Wilder Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Freedman Dramatic Agency Records, 1909-2011; Series IX
  - Musical works based on Thornton Wilder's plays, 1961–2008
    - Our Town film music correspondence, 2005 (Box 313, Folder 4163)
    - Our Town musical photocopied correspondence, 2002–2003 (Box 313, Folder 4164)
    - Music notes, clippings, and photocopied correspondence, circa 2002 (Box 313, Folder 4165)
    - Compact discs, 2005; undated (Box 313, Folder 4166)
      - Leonard Bernstein's "Peter Pan.", 2005; 1 (Box 433, Folder 5695)
      - Peter Vinograde piano music of Aaron Copland, Paul Creston, and Mark Zuckerman, 2001; 1 (Box 433, Folder 5696)
  - Scripts, screenplays, and related materials, 1964–2005
    - Grover's Corners materials, 1997–2003 (Box 314, Folder 4167-4168)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth musical, 1969 May (Box 314, Folder 4169)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth musical motion picture, undated (Box 314, Folder 4170)
    - Over and Over based on The Skin of Our Teeth materials, 2002 March–2003 (Box 314, Folder 4171-4173)
    - Dolly materials (working title), undated (Box 314, Folder 4174)
    - The Matchmaker French translation, circa 1955 (Box 315, Folder 4175)
    - Rules for Girls materials, 1991 October 18 (Box 315, Folder 4176)
      An adaptation of Heaven's My Destination.
    - The Eighth Day written for television, 1988 January 22 (Box 315, Folder 4177)
      Witten by Wendell Mayes.
    - The Eighth Day Hallmark Productions, 2001 March 20 (Box 315, Folder 4178)
    - The Eighth Day screenplay (Box 315, Folder 4179-4180)
    - The Ides of March screenplay, undated (Box 315, Folder 4181)
      Written by Franz Seitz.
    - Wilder Wiederentdeckt (Wilder Rediscovered) materials, 1999 (Box 315, Folder 4182)
    - Unsere Kleine Stadt (Our Town) materials, 2006 (Box 316, Folder 4183)
    - Nuestro Pueblo (Our Town) materials, undated (Box 316, Folder 4184)
    - Our Town (Chinese translation) photocopy, 1987 (Box 316, Folder 4185)
    - Our Town opera piano and vocal score, 2006 (Box 316, Folder 4186)
    - Our Town opera short score, 2004–2005 (Box 316, Folder 4187)
    - The Bridge of San Luis Rey materials, undated (Box 316, Folder 4188)
    - The Bridge of San Luis Rey a musical, 1992 April (Box 316, Folder 4189-4190)
    - Le Pont de San Luis Rey materials, 2004 (Box 317, Folder 4191)
    - The Bridge of San Luis Rey radio dramatization, undated (Box 317, Folder 4192)
      Written by Judith Adams.
    - Theophilius North materials, undated (Box 317, Folder 4193)
    - The American Drama and the New World Vision materials, 1981 (Box 317, Folder 4194)
      Esther Merle Jackson's dissertation.
    - Grover's Corners materials, 1984 September–1985 February (Box 317, Folder 4195-4196)
    - Our Town photocopy adaptation for Arena '59 and correspondence, 1964; undated (Box 317, Folder 4197)
    - Notre Petite Ville correspondence, circa 2007 (Box 318, Folder 4198-4201)
    - Heaven's My Destination screenplay, undated (Box 318, Folder 4202)
      Screenplay written by Ruth Gordon.
    - Heaven's My Destination materials, undated (Box 318, Folder 4203)
    - Hello Dolly! materials, circa 2010 (Box 319, Folder 4204)
    - Over and Over materials, 2002 March (Box 319, Folder 4205)
    - The Bridge of San Luis Rey materials, 2011 June 22 (Box 319, Folder 4206)
      Written by David Greenspan.
    - The Skin of Our Teeth musical, 2004 April (Box 319, Folder 4207-4208)
    - Theophilius North written for television, undated (Box 319, Folder 4209-4211)
    - One Act Plays French translations, circa 2008 (Box 319, Folder 4212)
      Written by James Costigan.
    - Pullman Car Hiawatha Opera in One Act, 2008 March 1 (Box 320, Folder 4213)
      Includes Le Long Festin de Noel, L'Ivresse des trois soeurs, L'Heureuse tranversee de New Jersey, and Le Train de Nuit Hiawatha.
    - The Ides of March English- German screenplay, undated (Box 320, Folder 4214)
      Music by David Winkler.
    - The Alcestiad or Life in the Sun materials
      - A Life in the Sun script, undated (Box 320, Folder 4215)
      - A Life in the Sun revision, 1955 August 25 (Box 320, Folder 4216)
      - The Alcestiad script, 1955 November 14 (Box 320, Folder 4217)
      - A Life in the Sun photocopied script, undated (Box 320, Folder 4218)
    - Girl Friday Productions' correspondence and Our Town photocopied scripts, 2007; undated (Box 320, Folder 4219)
    - Merchant of Yonkers scripts, undated (Box 321, Folder 4220-4224)
      Includes one typescript and one photocopy.
    - The Matchmaker script with annotations, undated (Box 321, Folder 4225-4226)
    - Short plays scripts
      - Infancy, undated (Box 321, Folder 4227)
      - Childhood, undated (Box 321, Folder 4228)
      - Youth, undated (Box 321, Folder 4229)
      - Infancy broadcast script, 1972 December (Box 321, Folder 4230)
      - Childhood broadcast script, 1972 December (Box 321, Folder 4231)
      - Childhood and The Drunken Sisters printed and photocopied scripts, undated (Box 321, Folder 4232)
      - The Wreck on the Five-Twenty Five, undated (Box 321, Folder 4233-4234)
      - The Wreck on the Five-Twenty Five related correspondence and photocopied notes and script, 1994–1995 (Box 322, Folder 4235)
        Includes on typescript and one photocopy.
      - A Ringing of Doorbells and The Rivers Under the Earth scripts, 1996 (Box 322, Folder 4236)
        Signed by F.J. O'Neil.
      - Shakespeare and the Bible script, undated (Box 322, Folder 4237)
      - Someone from Assissi script, undated (Box 322, Folder 4238)
      - Cement Hands script, undated (Box 322, Folder 4239)
      - Bernice script, undated (Box 322, Folder 4240)
      - The Unerring Instinct script, undated (Box 322, Folder 4241)
    - Translations and adaptations
      - Lucrece (rough copy) script, undated (Box 322, Folder 4242)
      - The Rape of Lucrece script, undated (Box 322, Folder 4244-4245)
      - Shadow of a Doubt photocopied screenplay and agreements, undated (Box 322, Folder 4246-4248)
      - Shadow of a Doubt photocopied screenplay and notes, 2005- (Box 323, Folder 4249-4250)
      - Shadow of a Doubt photocopied recopy screenplay, undated (Box 323, Folder 4251-4252)
      - Shadow of a Doubt typescript photocopy, undated (Box 323, Folder 4253-4254)
      - A Doll's House typescript, undated (Box 323, Folder 4255-4256)
  - Amos Niven Wilder materials
    Includes blank postcards, handwritten postcards, view books, and research notecards.
    - Blank cards, postcards, and viewbooks (Box 324)
    - Blank cards, postcards, and viewbooks (Box 325)
    - Blank cards, postcards, and viewbooks (Box 326)
    - Siena, Italy, undated (Box 327, Folder 4257)
    - New Hampshire and Massachusetts, United States, circa 1926 (Box 327, Folder 4258)
    - Basel, Switzerland, circa 1951 (Box 327, Folder 4259)
    - Jerusalem, undated (Box 327, Folder 4260)
    - Blank cards from Frances and Maine, United States, undated (Box 327, Folder 4261)
    - Italy, undated (Box 327, Folder 4262-4265)
    - Vaison La Romaine viewbook, undated (Box 327, Folder 4266)
    - Lake Maggiore, undated (Box 327, Folder 4267)
    - Ireland, undated (Box 327, Folder 4268)
    - Switzerland postcards and viewbook, undated (Box 327, Folder 4269)
      Handwritten postcard addressed to Amos Niven from "Lafe".
    - Annecy, France, undated (Box 327, Folder 4270)
    - Medieval glass windows, undated (Box 327, Folder 4271)
    - Nazareth, undated (Box 327, Folder 4272)
      A postcard from the British Museum.
    - Syrian dried flowers on cards, undated (Box 327, Folder 4273)
      Includes a handwritten postcard.
    - Oversized cards potentially from France, undated (Box 327, Folder 4274)
      Flowers from the Garden of Gethsemane and the Holy Land.
    - Tucson, Arizona postcards, undated (Box 327, Folder 4275)
      - Tennis players postcards, undated (Box 327, Folder 4276)
- Wiggin and Dana LLP Records, 1910-2012; Series X
  Wiggin and Dana LLP is a law firm that represents the Wilder family and the Wilder Family LLC. The Wilders' lawyers not only manage the literary properties of the family but also help maintain their estates. This series includes materials documenting the family's financials including estates, tax information, and trusts. The papers include materials about Thornton Wilder's works including agreements, royalty statements, and permissions.
  Materials in the series were kept in their original order and match the filing system that the firm had established. In many cases, the papers came in folders that had to be divided into multiple folders. The papers are organized into the following subseries: Subseries I: Taxes, royalties, and agreements, Subseries II: Thornton Wilder's works materials, Subseries III: Thornton Wilder collected materials.
  - Taxes, royalties, and agreements, 1928–2001
    - The Skin of Our Teeth materials
      - General correspondence, 1942–1975 (Box 328, Folder 4277-4279)
      - Documents, general, 1942–1967 (Box 328, Folder 4280-4281)
      - German translation, publication, and theatrical productions, 1950–1960 (Box 328, Folder 4282)
        Includes Thornton Wilder's handwritten correspondence.
      - Finnegan's Wake materials, 1942–1955 (Box 328, Folder 4283-4284)
        Includes contracts, clippings, and agreements.
      - Spanish translations, 1951–1962 (Box 328, Folder 4285)
      - Television rights, 1951–1964 (Box 328, Folder 4286)
      - Portuguese edition, 1961–1962 (Box 328, Folder 4287)
      - Drafts and extra copies, 1944–1957 (Box 328, Folder 4288)
    - Our Town materials
      - Correspondence, 1955–1962 (Box 329, Folder 4289-4291)
        Includes agreements and correspondence drafts.
      - Documents, general, 1939–1958 (Box 329, Folder 4292-4294)
      - Memoranda, 1941–1961 (Box 329, Folder 4295)
        Includes the note that original agreements are in J.D.D.'s safe.
      - Japanese translation, 1949–1963 (Box 329, Folder 4296)
      - Television contracts, 1953–1980 (Box 329, Folder 4297)
        Handwritten notes.
      - Argentine publication, 1943–1951 (Box 329, Folder 4298)
      - Radio contracts, 1940–1953 (Box 329, Folder 4299)
      - Italian translation, 1952–1964 (Box 329, Folder 4300)
      - Greek translation, 1953–1954 (Box 329, Folder 4301)
      - Franklin Publications Middle East translations, 1938–1955 (Box 329, Folder 4302)
      - U.S. Army Chinese Edition, 1955–1962 (Box 330, Folder 4303)
      - French translation, 1945–1959 (Box 330, Folder 4304)
      - Polish rights, 1957–1966 (Box 330, Folder 4305)
      - Recordings related materials, 1958–1961 (Box 330, Folder 4306)
      - Circle in the Square production materials, 1958–1959 (Box 330, Folder 4307)
      - Choate, Hall, and Stewart- Charles Playhouse, 1959–1960 (Box 330, Folder 4308)
      - Spanish rights and translation, 1944–1987 (Box 330, Folder 4309)
        Includes handwritten correspondence from Thornton Wilder to Thew Wright.
      - Hungarian production (Brandt and Brandt), 1960–1981 (Box 330, Folder 4310)
      - Portuguese language production, 1968 (Box 330, Folder 4311)
      - Drafts and extra copies, 1942–1949 (Box 330, Folder 4312-4313)
    - Rights of Albert and Charles Boni
      - Correspondence, 1963–1964 (Box 330, Folder 4314-4315)
      - Documents, 1955–1964 (Box 330, Folder 4316-4317)
      - Memoranda, 1960–1964 (Box 330, Folder 4318-4319)
      - Criterion Books, Inc. regarding "Trio" materials, 1946–1962 (Box 331, Folder 4320)
        Includes agreements, notes, and correspondence.
      - 1964 agreement, 1962–1964 (Box 331, Folder 4321-4322)
      - Contract with Albatross, 1947–1953 (Box 331, Folder 4323)
      - Drafts and extra copies, 1956–1963 (Box 331, Folder 4324)
    - Isabel Wilder tax returns and related materials
      - Income tax returns and estimates, 1947–1987 (Box 332, Folder 4325-4336)
        Includes lists of royalities, published works, and correspondence.
    - Trust with Thornton Wilder regarding publication and production matters
      - Our Town television agreement with Hartwest Productions, Inc., 1977 (Box 333, Folder 4337-4339)
      - Our Town grant of musical production rights to Mitchell and Neufeld, 1977–1998 (Box 333, Folder 4340-4343)
      - Our Town - TV exhibition of 1940 motion picture, 1982–1990 (Box 333, Folder 4344-4345)
      - Heaven's My Destination - Motion picture agreement with Aglim and Hoshire, 1982–1989 (Box 334, Folder 4346-4347)
      - The Skin of Our Teeth - Cable TV agreement with Limelight International, Inc., 1982–1989 (Box 334, Folder 4348)
        Includes materials detailing a claim of infringment by WHA-TV ("Sprockets" Series).
      - Agreement with S. Fischer Verlag for German production rights, 1982–1983 (Box 334, Folder 4349)
      - American Characteristics (collection of essays), 1979–1995 (Box 334, Folder 4350)
      - Agreement with Yale University Press for publication of the journals of Thornton Wilder, 1984–1986 (Box 334, Folder 4351)
    - Our Town musical agreements
      - Agreement with Marriott Lincolnshire Theater Corporation for production of Jones-Schmidt musical version, 1987–1992 (Box 334, Folder 4352-4353)
      - Lincoln Center production, 1988–1989 (Box 334, Folder 4354)
    - Thornton Wilder Trust No. II f.b.o Isabel Wilder
      - Documents and memos, 1963–1970 (Box 334, Folder 4355)
      - Trust agreement, 1964–1970 (Box 334, Folder 4356)
        Grant Nickerson, trustee. Includes documents pertaining to The Skin of Our Teeth musical.
      - Production agreement, 1963–1964 (Box 334, Folder 4357)
      - Consulting agreement with Isabel Wilder, 1964 (Box 334, Folder 4358)
      - Foreign bank accounts, 1964 (Box 334, Folder 4359)
      - Czechslovakian production, 1966 (Box 334, Folder 4360)
      - "Civilisation" project, 1970–1971 (Box 335, Folder 4361-4363)
      - Drafts and copies, 1963 (Box 335, Folder 4364)
      - Notes, agreements, and correspondence, 1992–1993 (Box 335, Folder 4365-4367)
        Includes Thornton Wilder's correspondence to Mary Ellen Bute.
    - Thornton Wilder's taxes
      - Income tax returns copies, 1945–1952 (Box 335, Folder 4368-4370)
      - Hamden tax lists copies, 1929–1950 (Box 336, Folder 4371)
      - Tax on bonds copies, 1939–1942 (Box 336, Folder 4372)
        Includes notes and correspondence in Thornton Wilder's handwriting.
      - British income tax returns copies, 1930–1931 (Box 336, Folder 4373)
    - German royalty statements, 1958 (Box 336, Folder 4374)
    - Royalty statements
      - Foreign and domestic royalty statements, 1957–1959 (Box 336, Folder 4375-4378)
      - Samuel French, Ltd., 1955–1957 (Box 336, Folder 4379-4380)
      - The Matchmaker New York production on tour, 1957 (Box 337, Folder 4381-4383)
      - The Matchmaker royalty statements, 1956–1957 (Box 337, Folder 4384-4386)
      - Japanese royalty statements and foreign rights, 1952–1957 (Box 337, Folder 4387)
      - Italian royalty statements, 1952–1956 (Box 337, Folder 4388-4389)
      - Brandt and Brandt Dramatic Inc. materials, 1955 (Box 337, Folder 4390-4391)
      - German royalties, 1950–1956 (Box 337, Folder 4392-4393)
      - Scandanavia and the Netherlands royalties, 1954–1956 (Box 338, Folder 4394)
      - Harper & Brothers- Coward McCann Inc., 1953–1956 (Box 338, Folder 4395-4396)
      - Miscellaneous royalty statements, 1956–1957 (Box 338, Folder 4397)
      - Deposit of manuscript and material with Yale University Library, 1951–1961 (Box 338, Folder 4398)
      - De Sica correspondence and agreements, 1952 (Box 338, Folder 4399)
      - Tallulah Bankhead's book, 1952 August (Box 338, Folder 4400)
      - Miscellaneous rights, 1938 September (Box 338, Folder 4401)
        Includes Thornton Wilder's undated correspondence addressed to Thew Wright.
      - Samuel French Ltd. royalty statements, 1944–1954 (Box 338, Folder 4402-4404)
      - Mr. and Mrs. Leonard Trolley application for visa to enter U.S., 1946–1948 (Box 338, Folder 4405)
    - Thornton Wilder financial matters
      Includes a memo written by Thornton Wilder.
      - List of investments, 1940–1965 (Box 338, Folder 4406-4407)
      - Wiggin and Dana bills, 1966–1969 (Box 338, Folder 4408)
      - Japanese investments, 1956–1968 (Box 338, Folder 4409)
      - Foreign bank accounts, 1962–1968 (Box 339, Folder 4410)
      - Social Security and Medicare, 1966–1971 (Box 339, Folder 4411)
    - Thew Wright Jr. Trustee f.o.b. Isabel Wilder regarding The Alcestaid
      - Correspondence, 1955–1978 (Box 339, Folder 4412-4413)
      - J.D. Dana's cash accounts, 1929–1969 (Box 339, Folder 4414-4417)
      - Documents, 1955–1958 (Box 339, Folder 4418)
      - Royalties, 1955–1982 (Box 339, Folder 4419-4421)
        Includes cash accounts copies, lists of investments, receipts, and Broker's statements. Also includes correspondence in Thornton Wilder's handwriting.
      - Opera based on The Alcestiad materials, 1955–1982 (Box 340, Folder 4422)
        Includes typescript and photocopies of agreements with S. Fischer Verlag.
      - German translation materials, 1959–1971 (Box 340, Folder 4423)
      - Epilogue: The Three Drunken Sisters, 1957–1982 (Box 340, Folder 4424)
    - Trust f.o.b. Isabel Wilder with Grant Nickerson as trustee
      - Correspondence, 1958–1985 (Box 340, Folder 4425-4427)
      - Documents, 1958–1981 (Box 340, Folder 4428-4430)
      - Memoranda, 1964–1978 (Box 340, Folder 4431)
      - Accounts, 1958–1985 (Box 340, Folder 4432-4433)
        Includes copyright assignments, agreements, and correspondence.
      - Income tax, 1959–1986 (Box 340, Folder 4434-4436)
      - Childhood materials, 1960–1967 (Box 341, Folder 4437)
      - The Long Christmas Dinner - Hindemith opera, 1961–1975 (Box 341, Folder 4438)
      - Amateur production rights, 1958–1963 (Box 341, Folder 4439)
      - Drafts and extra copies, 1958–1991 (Box 341, Folder 4440)
    - Trust f.b.o. Isabel Wilder regarding The Ides of March motion picture rights, 1986–1988 (Box 341, Folder 4441)
    - Thornton Wilder: Specific matters
      - The Cabala materials, 1943–1982 (Box 341, Folder 4442)
      - The Angel that Trouble the Waters materials, 1949–1963 (Box 341, Folder 4443)
      - The Woman of Andros materials, 1930–1965 (Box 341, Folder 4444)
      - The Flight into Egypt materials, 1955 (Box 341, Folder 4445)
        Includes correspondence, agreements, and notes.
      - A Doll's House (translation) materials, 1943 (Box 341, Folder 4446)
        Includes an assignment of copyright, correspondence, and notes. Also includes Thornton Wilder's correspondence addressed to Thew Wright.
      - Goethe lectures, 1949–1955 (Box 341, Folder 4447)
      - Harvard lectures, 1949–1955 (Box 341, Folder 4448)
      - Dr. Emil Oprecht materials, 1944–1952 (Box 341, Folder 4449)
      - T.V. guest appearances materials, 1952 (Box 341, Folder 4450)
      - The Atlantic Monthly correspondence, 1952–1960 (Box 341, Folder 4451)
        Includes correspondence and notes.
      - The Silent Generation correspondence, 1954–1963 (Box 341, Folder 4452)
      - Mondadori Publishing Company Inc. regarding BMM edition, 1957–1964 (Box 341, Folder 4453)
      - Agreements with Mondadori, 1963–1973 (Box 341, Folder 4454-4455)
      - Three Plays correspondence, 1955–1964 (Box 341, Folder 4456-4457)
      - Three Plays contract with Longmans Green & Co. Ltd, 1948–1958 (Box 342, Folder 4458)
      - The Trumpet Shall Sound materials, 1919–1958 (Box 342, Folder 4459)
      - United States Information Agency, 1958–1961 (Box 342, Folder 4460)
        Includes materials related to Our Town, The Skin of Our Teeth, and The Matchmaker.
      - Albert Schweitzer Hospital Fund, 1954–1961 (Box 342, Folder 4461)
      - E. Frederick Davies correspondence, 1959 (Box 342, Folder 4462)
      - Aguilar S.A. de Ediciones- Spanish Publications, 1959–1964 (Box 342, Folder 4463)
      - An Evening with Thornton Wilder - a recording, 1962–1966 (Box 342, Folder 4464)
      - The Warship, 1962–1963 (Box 342, Folder 4465)
      - The Entertainers by Roddy McDowall, circa 1965 (Box 342, Folder 4466)
      - Assignment by Harold Mantell, Inc of motion picture Thornton Wilder, 1968 (Box 342, Folder 4467)
      - Gifts to Yale of manuscripts and papers, 1969 (Box 342, Folder 4468)
        Contributions by Thornton Wilder.
      - Action v. Twentieth Century Fox regarding "Dolly" soundtrack album, 1971–1972 (Box 342, Folder 4469)
    - Thornton Wilder regarding Isabel Wilder: salary and other matters
      Includes correspondence addressed to John Barnett in Thornton Wilder's handwriting.
      - Correspondence, 1949–1986 (Box 342, Folder 4470-4472)
      - Documents, 1954–1966 (Box 342, Folder 4473-4474)
      - Employer's quarterly federal tax returns, 1949–1965 (Box 342, Folder 4475-4476)
      - Isabel Wilder gift tax returns, 1976–1977 (Box 342, Folder 4477)
    - Thornton Wilder trust No. III f.b.o. Charlotte Wilder (Box 342)
      - Correspondence, 1966–1976 (Box 342, Folder 4478-4479)
      - Documents, 1972–1974 (Box 343, Folder 4480)
      - Memos, 1966–1967 (Box 343, Folder 4481)
      - Union Trust account statements, 1966–1977 (Box 343, Folder 4482-4485)
        Includes copies of a trust agreement.
    - Thornton Wilder income taxes
      Includes The Estate Analyst, notes, and the Thornton Wilder Agency list of expenses.
      - Income and gift taxes, 1966–1969 (Box 343, Folder 4486-4487)
      - Income taxes, 1968 (Box 343, Folder 4488)
      - Income taxes, 1969 (Box 343, Folder 4489-4490)
        Includes handwritten correspondence addressed to Grant N. Nickerson.
      - Tax returns and estimates, 1970 (Box 343, Folder 4491-4492)
        Includes Thornton Wilder's handwritten notes.
      - Tax returns and estimates, 1971 (Box 344, Folder 4493-4494)
      - Declaration return, 1972–1974 (Box 344, Folder 4495-4496)
        Includes notes written in Thornton Wilder's hand.
      - Tax returns and estimates, 1973–1974 (Box 344, Folder 4497-4498)
        Includes notes written in Thornton Wilder's hand which includes a statement of professional expenditures.
      - Tax returns and estimates, 1974 (Box 344, Folder 4499)
        Includes reciepts and notes.
    - Our Town radio broadcast related correspondence, 1938–1946 (Box 344, Folder 4500-4502)
    - Thornton Wilder income tax and other tax matters
      - Correspondence, 1943–1975 (Box 344, Folder 4503-4505)
        Included in a folder labeled "correspondence- general from January 1, 1949 to December 31, 1953 and regarding A Doll's House and Frank N. Magill.
      - Documents, 1944–1955 (Box 344, Folder 4506)
      - Income tax materials, 1935–1938 (Box 344, Folder 4507)
      - Claim for refund of British and Canadian income taxes, 1946–1955 (Box 345, Folder 4508)
      - Memos, 1945–1965 (Box 345, Folder 4509)
        Includes notes and Internal Revenue Service documents.
      - Massachusetts income tax, 1953 (Box 345, Folder 4510)
      - Gift tax return, 1959–1963 (Box 345, Folder 4511)
      - Extra copies and drafts, 1945–1953 (Box 345, Folder 4512)
      - Claim for exemption from United Kingdom income tax, 1957–1973 (Box 345, Folder 4513)
      - Claim for exemption from taxes of Federal Republic of Germany, 1971–1981 (Box 345, Folder 4514)
      - Argentine income tax, 1973 April (Box 345, Folder 4515)
      - French witholding tax, 1974 March (Box 345, Folder 4516)
    - Thornton Wilder regarding The Bridge of San Luis Rey
      - General correspondence, 1946–1986 (Box 345, Folder 4517-4519)
      - Documents- general, 1931–1964 (Box 345, Folder 4520)
      - Japanese translation, 1949–1960 (Box 345, Folder 4521)
      - German translation, 1949–1958 (Box 345, Folder 4522)
        Includes request for permission to reprint, notes, and royalty reports.
      - Spanish translations, 1944–1959 (Box 345, Folder 4523)